Blazor Web App (C#)
Author: Microsoft
Description: A project template for creating a Blazor web app that supports both server-side rendering and client interactivity. This template can be used for web apps with rich dynamic user interfaces (UIs).
This template contains technologies from parties other than Microsoft, see https://aka.ms/aspnetcore/11.0-third-party-notices for details.

Usage:
  dotnet new blazor [options] [template options]

Options:
  -n, --name <name>       The name for the output being created. If no name is specified, the name of the output directory is used.
  -o, --output <output>   Location to place the generated output.
  --dry-run               Displays a summary of what would happen if the given command line were run if it would result in a template creation. [default: False]
  --force                 Forces content to be generated even if it would change existing files. [default: False]
  --no-update-check       Disables checking for the template package updates when instantiating a template. [default: False]
  --project <project>     The project that should be used for context evaluation.
  -lang, --language <C#>  Specifies the template language to instantiate.
  --type <project>        Specifies the template type to instantiate.

Template options:
  -f, --framework <net10.0|net11.0|net8.0|net9.0>       The target framework for the project.
                                                        Type: choice
                                                          net11.0  
                                                          net10.0  Target net10.0
                                                          net9.0   Target net9.0
                                                          net8.0   Target net8.0
                                                        Default: net11.0
  --no-restore                                          If specified, skips the automatic restore of the project on create.
                                                        Type: bool
                                                        Default: false
  --exclude-launch-settings                             Whether to exclude launchSettings.json from the generated template.
                                                        Type: bool
                                                        Default: false
  -int, --interactivity <Auto|None|Server|WebAssembly>  Chooses which interactive render mode to use for interactive components
                                                        Type: choice
                                                          None         No interactivity (static server rendering only)
                                                          Server       Runs on the server
                                                          WebAssembly  Runs in the browser using WebAssembly
                                                          Auto         Uses Server while downloading WebAssembly assets, then uses WebAssembly
                                                        Default: Server
  -e, --empty                                           Configures whether to omit sample pages and styling that demonstrate basic usage patterns.
                                                        Type: bool
                                                        Default: false
  -au, --auth <Individual|None>                         The type of authentication to use
                                                        Type: choice
                                                          None        No authentication
                                                          Individual  Individual authentication
                                                        Default: None
  -uld, --use-local-db                                  Whether to use LocalDB instead of SQLite. This option only applies if --auth Individual is specified.
                                                        Type: bool
                                                        Default: false
  -ai, --all-interactive                                Configures whether to make every page interactive by applying an interactive render mode at the top level. If false, pages will use static server rendering by default, and can be marked interactive on a per-page or per-component basis.
                                                        Enabled if: (InteractivityPlatform != "None")
                                                        Type: bool
                                                        Default: false
  --no-https                                            Whether to turn off HTTPS. This option only applies if Individual isn't used for --auth.
                                                        Type: bool
                                                        Default: false
  --use-program-main                                    Whether to generate an explicit Program class and Main method instead of top-level statements.
                                                        Type: bool
                                                        Default: false
  --localhost-tld                                       Whether to combine the project name with the .dev.localhost TLD in the application URL for local development, e.g. https://myapp.dev.localhost:12345.
                                                        Type: bool
                                                        Default: false

